<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>XSCALE News</title>
  <subtitle>An Honorable Agile Ecosystem</subtitle>
  <id>https://xscalealliance.org/news</id>
  <link href="https://xscalealliance.org/news"/>
  <link href="https://xscalealliance.org/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2018-02-13T00:59:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Peter Merel</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>XSCALE partnering with ABC</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://xscalealliance.org/news/2018/02/13/abc.html"/>
    <id>https://xscalealliance.org/news/2018/02/13/abc.html</id>
    <published>2018-02-13T00:59:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-14T19:22:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;XSCALE Alliance has agreed to a &lt;strong&gt;Memorandum of Understanding&lt;/strong&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.agilebusiness.org/"&gt;Agile Business Consortium&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align="center"&gt; &lt;img src="/img/x-abc-400.png" /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This memorandum of understanding between XSCALE Alliance (“XA”) and the Agile Business Consortium (“ABC”) expresses an alignment and convergence of will between the two. It represents a treaty for the mutual benefit of the members of both communities. &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;ABC is an organization promoting the growth of communities working to advance the state of the art in Business Agility. It now recognises XSCALE Alliance as another such community.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;XSCALE Alliance is a principled ecosystem of independent agile service providers who develop, share, coach and train agile practice-pattern languages including Exponential Business Agility (“XBA”) which covers de-scaling, throughput accounting, and self-propagating transformation. It works to generate self-directing portfolios of self-managing streams of self-organizing teams.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;ABC and XA have agreed that ABC and XSCALE practice patterns are interoperable, and the two organizations will work together to promote their interoperation. This work will include cross-promotion, discounts for members on training and events, and cross-linkage between each others’ knowledge bases.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;In particular, ABC will extend free institutional membership to XA. XA will extend a free partnership to ABC. These arrangements entail:
(4.1) 30% discount on XA Practitioner training for all individual ABC members.
(4.2) 30% discount on XA Coach training for all qualified individual ABC members.
(4.3) 30% discount for ABC members on tickets to XA workshops and conferences.
(4.4) Individual ABC membership to the XA stewards
(4.5) 30% discount on ABC membership to all XA Coaches and Practitioners&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The senior members of both organizations will work to align their respective collateral to provide a consistent conceptual framework for business agility:
(5.1) XA will work to integrate with ABC’s business agility taxonomy as it becomes available.
(5.2) ABC will link to or integrate XSCALE content into its knowledge base under a suitable open content license”&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;13 Feb 2018 by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/geofellingham/"&gt;Geof Ellingham&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/petermerel/"&gt;Peter Merel&lt;/a&gt; for XSCALE Alliance and Agile Business Consortium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id="why-is-this-mou-important-to-xscale-alliance"&gt;Why is this MOU important to XSCALE Alliance?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where the DSDM practices and &lt;a href="https://www.agilebusiness.org/communities/framework-for-business-agility/"&gt;Framework for Business Agility&lt;/a&gt; respect the structures of traditional organizations, XSCALE principles and practices generate &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLcF9BigzPGr3Fsema6jErOT8xwz0HR7NU"&gt;self-directing portfolios of self-managing streams of self-organizing teams&lt;/a&gt;. In many cases these two approaches are complementary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So XSCALE Alliance and The Agile Business Consortium, formerly the &lt;a href="https://www.agilebusiness.org/resources/dsdm-handbooks/the-dsdm-agile-project-framework-2014-onwards"&gt;DSDM Consortium&lt;/a&gt;, are also complementary. As XA and ABC are both signatories to the &lt;a href="http://agnosticagile.org/"&gt;Agnostic Agile Oath&lt;/a&gt; an initiative of XSCALE Alliance Steward &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/adrianlander/"&gt;Adrian Lander&lt;/a&gt;, this MOU supports practitioners combining XSCALE and ABC practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XSCALE Alliance applauds the Agile Business Consortium as a global champion in promoting business agility. Represented by Arie Van Bennekum, ABC helped author the original &lt;a href="http://agilemanifesto.org/"&gt;Agile Manifesto&lt;/a&gt; and organizes the world's longest running &lt;a href="https://www.agileconference.org/"&gt;Agile Business Conference&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XA and ABC also maintain MOUs of interoperation with the &lt;a href="https://xscalealliance.org/news/2018/01/27/bai.html"&gt;Business Agile Institute&lt;/a&gt;. While some people in the Agile Industrial Complex enjoy scrapping over frameworks, our ecosystem focuses on business throughput first, tailoring the most effective combination of practice patterns to achieve it.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>XSCALE Alliance sponsors Agility Today Unconference</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://xscalealliance.org/news/2018/02/03/agilitytoday.html"/>
    <id>https://xscalealliance.org/news/2018/02/03/agilitytoday.html</id>
    <published>2018-02-03T00:59:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-14T19:22:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p align="center"&gt;&lt;a href="https://agilitytoday.com/about.html"&gt;&lt;img src="/img/agility-today.png" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
XSCALE Alliance proudly sponsors the Agility Today UnConference in Delhi-NCR, 24-25 February 2018, gathering the most progressive agile ecosystem in India. &lt;a href="https://lnkd.in/f2BM4W9"&gt;Details Here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>XSCALE partnering with BAI</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://xscalealliance.org/news/2018/01/27/bai.html"/>
    <id>https://xscalealliance.org/news/2018/01/27/bai.html</id>
    <published>2018-01-27T00:59:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-14T19:22:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;XSCALE Alliance has agreed to a &lt;strong&gt;Memorandum of Understanding&lt;/strong&gt; with &lt;a href="https://businessagility.institute/"&gt;Business Agility Institute&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align="center"&gt; &lt;img src="/img/x-b-400.png" /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Business Agility Institute ("BAI") and XSCALE Alliance ("XA") enjoy strong thematic alignment. &lt;strong&gt;BAI&lt;/strong&gt; is an advocacy, membership and research organization that promotes the structure, mindset, and behaviour of an agile organisation. &lt;strong&gt;XA&lt;/strong&gt; is a Linux-style ecosystem of independent service providers that promotes specific agile organisation principles and practice-patterns. This Memorandum is to confirm the commitment of the two to interoperate for the mutual benefit of all members.  
In 2018 each will offer the following benefits:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;XA extends partnership to BAI:
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;30% discount on &lt;strong&gt;Practitioner Training&lt;/strong&gt; for all individual BAI members.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;30% discount on &lt;strong&gt;Coach Training&lt;/strong&gt; for all qualified individual BAI members.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;BAI extends &lt;strong&gt;Institutional Membership&lt;/strong&gt; to XA:
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Individual membership to the &lt;strong&gt;XA Stewards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;30% discount on BAI membership to all &lt;strong&gt;XA Coaches and Practitioners&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;30% discount code for the &lt;strong&gt;Business Agility Conference&lt;/strong&gt; series to all XA members&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;The senior members of both organizations will align their respective collateral to provide a consistent conceptual framework for business agility:
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;XA will integrate with and apply BAI's &lt;strong&gt;Business Agility Taxonomy&lt;/strong&gt; and assessment tools as they become available.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;BAI will link to or integrate XA &lt;strong&gt;Practice Pattern Languages&lt;/strong&gt; into the Institute knowledge base under an open content license&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;27 January 2018 by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/evanleybourn/"&gt;Evan Leybourn&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/petermerel/"&gt;Peter Merel&lt;/a&gt; for XSCALE Alliance and Business Agility Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id="why-is-this-mou-important-to-xscale-alliance"&gt;Why is this MOU important to XSCALE Alliance?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evan Leybourn’s BAI ran the world’s first Business Agility Conference in New York in 2017 and lit the way forward with the most comprehensive and detailed taxonomy of agile organization today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XSCALE’s principles and pattern languages provide an agnostic praxis to fulfil the BAI taxonomy., We’re chopping down the Agile greasy pole of vanity certificates to provide a #NoFramework ecosystem of independent coaches collaborating on the Linux of the agile world - an open content kernel wrapped in commercial training, coaching and tooling products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XSCALE has signed an MOU with BAI to make it clear that each supports the other. People scrap over Agile frameworks but for us these arguments fall away when we focus on business throughput first. Which is why we say Agile in IT is nonsense. Meaningful agility lives and dies with the business.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
